Contact

aditivohra2005@rediffmail.c

www.linkedin.com/in/aditi-vohrab8ba6b195 (LinkedIn)

Top Skills

IT Service Management
IT Strategy
Strategic Planning

Aditi Vohra

Senior Training Consultant at SpireTec Solutions New Delhi

Summary

Experienced Senior Training Consultant with a demonstrated history of working in the information technology and services industry. Skilled in Strategic Planning, IT Service Management, IT Strategy, Program Management, and Project Management. Strong human resources professional with a Bachelor's degree focused in Business, Management, Marketing, and Related Support Services from Delhi University.

Experience

SpireTec Solutions
Senior Training Consultant
October 2019 - Present (11 months)
New Delhi Area, India

Freelancer

IT Support Specialist
October 2015 - October 2019 (4 years 1 month)

Education

Delhi University

Bachelor's degree, Business, Management, Marketing, and Related Support Services · (2010 - 2013)